https://www.artima.com/termsofuse.html

The Artima Network's Terms of Use Agreement
Artima, Inc. ("Artima") welcomes you to the Artima Network and asks you to review and agree to this Terms of Use
Agreement (the "Agreement") before using the network. The Artima Network consists of (a) Web Sites, including Artima
Developer at www.artima.com; and (b) email mailing lists, such as those at lists.artima.com.
YOU AGREE TO READ THIS AGREEMENT BEFORE USING THE ARTIMA NETWORK.
THESE TERMS ARE ENTERED INTO BY AND BETWEEN ARTIMA
AND YOU, AND YOU ACCEPT THEM BY: (a) PLACING AN ORDER THROUGH AN ARTIMA NETWORK WEB SITE; (b) USING AN ARTIMA NETWORK
WEB SITE IN ANY OTHER MANNER; AND/OR (c) ACKNOWLEDGING AGREEMENT WITH THIS AGREEMENT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ALL OF
THE TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT, DO NOT USE THE ARTIMA NETWORK.
1. DESCRIPTION OF SERVICE. Artima offers certain services to you on the Artima Network, including discussion
forums, blogs, articles, zines, news, chapters, RSS aggregators, and mailing lists, through its network of properties which may be
accessed through any various medium or device now known or hereafter developed (the "Service").
You also understand and agree that the Service may include advertisements and that these advertisements are necessary for Artima
to provide the Service.
Artima reserves the right to refuse Service to any user.
2. REGISTRATION. In order to use certain parts of the Service, you must register and complete
the Artima Network's registration screen. As part of the registration process, you agree: (a) to
provide certain limited information about you as prompted by a registration form (such information to be current, complete
and accurate); (b) to submit a valid e-mail address and select a password; (c) to be responsible for all uses of your
accountwhether or not you have authorized such useand for maintaining the confidentiality of your password;
(d) to notify Artima immediately of any unauthorized use of your account; (e) that you are at least 13 years of age;
and (f) to maintain and update this information as required to keep it current, complete and accurate. The information
requested during the registration process shall be referred to as registration data (the "Registration Data").
You
accept all risks of unauthorized access to Registration Data.
Artima reserves the right to delete
accounts created by users who appropriate the name, likeness, email address, or other personally identifiable information
of another individual.
Artima will not be held liable for any loss or damage for non-compliance with this Agreement.
3. USER CONDUCT. As part of Artima Network's community of users, you will naturally agree to act responsibly and to treat
other users with respect.
You have sole responsibility for adequate protection and backup of data and/or equipment used
in connection with the Service.
4. CONTENT. You are fully responsible for any data, text, software, music, sound, photographs, graphics, video,
messages, or other materials ("Content") you upload, post, or otherwise transmit on or via the Service
including, but not limited to forum posts, articles, news stories, blogs, and e-mail messagesand the consequences of any such Content.
You agree not to post any Content that violates this Agreement or which might be offensive, illegal, or harm the safety of or
violate the rights of others and are fully responsible for any Content that you do post. You understand and agree that Artima
may review from time to time and delete any Content, including Content that violates this Agreement or which might be offensive,
illegal, or harm the safety of or violate the rights of others. Content that is illegal or prohibited ("Prohibited
Content"), includes, but is not limited to, Content that:
Is unlawful, harassing, libelous, abusive, threatening, harmful, bigoted, racially offensive, obscene, defamatory, vulgar, pornographic, profane, indecent or otherwise objectionable.
Displays sexually explicit material of any kind.
Encourages conduct that could constitute a criminal offense, gives rise to civil liability or otherwise violates any applicable local, state, national or international law or regulation.
Transmits or posts any unsolicited or unauthorized advertising, "spam," junk mail, "chain letters," "pyramid schemes," etc.
Transmits or posts any Content that infringes upon patents, trademarks, trade secrets, copyrights or other proprietary rights.
Transmits or posts any viruses or material designed to disrupt, limit or destroy any functionality of any computer software or hardware of users or the
Service.
Collects, stores or solicits information about other users for commercial or unlawful purposes or engages in commercial activity such as contests, sweepstakes, etc. without Artima's prior written consent.
Contains personally identifiable information about another individual that was published without their express consent.
Advertises any illegal services or the sale of any items prohibited or restricted by applicable law.
Has misleading email addresses or other manipulated identifiers to disguise its origin.
Artima does not claim ownership of the Content you submit or make available for inclusion on the Service and shall have no obligation of
any kind with respect to such Content. Unless otherwise stated herein or in Artima's Privacy Policy, any Content you submit or make
available for inclusion on the Service shall be deemed to be provided on a nonconfidential basis ("the Nonconfidential Content"). Some Content you
submit or make available for inclusion on the Service may be governed by a separate agreement between you and Artima, such as an
"Author's Agreement" for original articles you write and submit to Artima for publication, which defines the license you grant to Artima for
that Content. Unless governed by such a separate agreement between you and Artima, Artima shall be free to use or disseminate Nonconfidential Content
on an unrestricted basis for any purpose, and you grant Artima an irrevocable, worldwide, royalty-free, nonexclusive
license to use, copy, license, reproduce, modify, distribute, transmit, display, perform, adapt, resell, publish, and otherwise exploit such
Content (including in digital form). You represent and warrant that you have proper authorization for the worldwide transfer and processing
among Artima, its affiliates, and third-party providers of any Content that you may provide on the Service.
5. PRIVACY. Please see our Privacy Policy incorporated herein by reference.
6. COPYRIGHT.
Please see our Copyright Notice incorporated herein by reference.
7. TERMINATION. Artima reserves the right to refuse service to anyone in its sole discretion. Artima may terminate your Service and remove
any and all Information, Content, postings or communications at any time, without notice, for conduct that violates this Agreement.
8. ADVERTISEMENTS AND PROMOTIONS.
Artima runs advertisements and promotions from third parties on the Website. Your correspondence or business
dealings with, or participation in promotions of, advertisers other than Artima found on or through an Artima Network Web Site, including payment
and delivery of related goods or services, and any other terms, conditions, warranties or representations associated with such dealings, are solely
between you and such advertiser. Artima is not responsible or liable for any loss or damage of any sort incurred as the result of any such
dealings or as the result of the presence of such non-Artima advertisers on an Artima Network Web Site.
9. CONTENT PROVIDED VIA LINKS.
You may find links to other Internet sites or resources on an Artima Network Web Site. You acknowledge and agree
that Artima is not responsible for the availability of such external sites or resources, and does not endorse and is not responsible or liable for
any content, advertising, products, or other materials on or available from such sites or resources. Artima will not be responsible or liable, directly
or indirectly, for any actual or alleged damage or loss caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods or services
available on or through any such site or resource.
10. MODIFICATION. WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO MODIFY THIS AGREEMENT AT ANY TIME BY POSTING THE AMENDED TERMS ON THE ARTIMA NETWORK. Your continued use
of the Artima Network indicates your acceptance of any amendments to the Agreement.
11. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES. YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT USE OF THE SERVICES AND/OR ANY GRAPHICS OR OTHER CONTENT YOU DOWNLOAD FROM THE ARTIMA NETWORK
IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK AND THAT YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF
FILES, SOFTWARE, SERVICES AND/OR ANY GRAPHICS OR OTHER CONTENT. THE SERVICES AND/OR ANY GRAPHICS OR OTHER CONTENT YOU DOWNLOAD FROM THE ARTIMA NETWORK
ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS. ARTIMA, ITS LICENSORS AND SUPPLIERS EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS, IMPLIED, STATUTORY
OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. NEITHER
ARTIMA NOR ITS LICENSORS OR SUPPLIERS MAKE ANY WARRANTY THAT THE SOFTWARE, SERVICES AND/OR ANY GRAPHICS OR OTHER CONTENT YOU DOWNLOAD FROM THE ARTIMA
NETWORK WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS, OR THAT THE SOFTWARE OR SERVICE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE, OR ERROR FREE; NOR DOES ARTIMA, ITS LICENSORS
OR SUPPLIERS MAKE ANY WARRANTY AS TO THE RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM THE USE OF ANY SERVICE OR AS TO THE ACCURACY OR RELIABILITY OF ANY INFORMATION
OBTAINED THROUGH ANY SERVICE OR THAT DEFECTS IN THE SOFTWARE WILL BE CORRECTED. ARTIMA DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE ARTIMA NETWORK OR THE SERVERS THAT MAKE
IT AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS.
SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF CERTAIN WARRANTIES, SO SOME OF THE ABOVE
EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
12. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY. TO THE FULL EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, ARTIMA, ITS LICENSORS OR SUPPLIERS SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT,
INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, RESULTING FROM THE USE OR THE INABILITY TO USE THE SOFTWARE, SERVICE, AND/OR ANY GRAPHICS OR OTHER
CONTENT, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, GOODWILL, USE, REVENUE OR OTHER ECONOMIC ADVANTAGE EVEN IF ARTIMA HAS BEEN
ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES OR COULD HAVE REASONABLY FORESEEN THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, HOWEVER THEY ARISE, WHETHER IN BREACH
OF CONTRACT OR TORT. FURTHER, ARTIMA SHALL HAVE NO LIABILITY FOR ANY THIRD PARTY CONTENT UPLOADED ONTO OR DOWNLOADED FROM THE SERVICE. TO THE EXTENT
THAT ANY JURSIDICTION DOES NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, PORITONS OF THE ABOVE
LIMITATIONS OR EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT APPLY.
13. INDEMNITY. You hereby agree, at your expense, to indemnify, defend and hold Artima and its affiliates, shareholders, officers, directors,
agents, licensors, suppliers, partners, employees and representatives
harmless from and against any claim or demand, including any losses,
costs, damages, liability, and/or expense made by a third party arising out of or relating to (a) your violation of rights of others, (b) your
fraud or manipulation, or other breach of this Agreement, or (c) your use of the Artima Network, any service, or software.
14. ARTIMA TRADEMARKS NOTICE. The term "Artima" and all graphic images associated with the site are trademarks or registered trademarks of
Artima, Inc. All other company and/or product names may be trademarks or registered trademarks of their owners.
15. GENERAL TERMS. This Agreement is governed in all respects by the laws of the State of California, U.S.A, without reference to its conflicts of
laws, principles and any dispute arising hereunder shall be submitted to state and federal courts in San Mateo, California and you consent to the
exclusive jurisdiction of such courts. If any provision of this Agreement is held to be invalid or unenforceable, such provision shall be struck
and the remaining provisions shall be enforced. Artima's failure to act with respect to a breach by you does not waive Artima's right to act with
respect to subsequent or similar breaches. You may not assign or transfer this Agreement or any rights hereunder, and any attempt to the contrary
is void. This Agreement shall inure to the benefit of and be binding upon each party's successors and assigns. Artima shall not be liable for any
delay or failure to perform resulting directly or indirectly from any causes beyond Artima's reasonable control. Any notice required or given to
you under this Agreement shall be delivered by electronic mail at the e-mail address provided by you during registration.
16. SPECIAL ADMONITIONS FOR INTERNATIONAL USE. As a consequence of the global nature of the Internet, you agree to comply with all local rules
regarding user conduct on the Internet and acceptable Content. Specifically, you agree to comply with all applicable laws regarding the transmission
of technical data exported from the United States or the country in which you reside or use the Service.
17. ENTIRE UNDERSTANDING. This Agreement, together with Artima's Privacy Policy and Copyright Notice constitute the complete and exclusive
understanding and agreement of the parties relating to the subject matter hereof and supersedes all prior understandings, proposals,
agreements, negotiations, and discussions between the parties, whether written or oral. Artima reserves the right to change this Agreement
and the terms of the Privacy Policy and Copyright Notice from time to time. You understand and agree that you are solely responsible for
reviewing the terms of this Agreement, the Privacy Policy and the Copyright Notice from time to time. Any continued use of any software or
service by you after such amended terms have been posted or information regarding such amendment has been sent to you, shall be deemed your
consent and agreement to such amended terms.
Artima provides consulting and training services to help you make the most of Scala, reactive
and functional programming, enterprise systems, big data, and testing.
Artima, Inc.
2070 N Broadway Unit 305
Walnut Creek CA 94597
USA
(925) 394-7298 (Phone)
(925) 394-7299 (Fax)
Copyright © 1996-2020 Artima, Inc. All Rights Reserved. - Privacy Policy - Terms of Use
Copyright © 1996-2020 Artima, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
